Based on the incredible true lie.
J.T. LeRoy is a drama, history film directed by Justin Kelly.
A young woman named Savannah Knoop spends six years pretending to be a transgender
writer named JT Leroy, the made-up literary persona of her sister-in-law.
Savannah Knoop, played by Kristen Stewart.
Laura Albert, played by Laura Dern.
Eva, played by Diane Kruger.
Geoffrey Knoop, played by Jim Sturgess.
Sasha, played by Courtney Love.
Sean, played by Kelvin Harrison, Jr..
JT LeRoy is a 2018 biographical drama film directed by Justin Kelly based on the
memoir Girl Boy Girl: How I Became JT Leroy by Savannah Knoop.
It stars Kristen Stewart, Laura Dern, Kelvin Harrison Jr., Diane Kruger,
James Jagger, Dave Brown, Jim Sturgess and Courtney Love.
It had its world premiere as the closing night film of the
2018 Toronto International Film Festival.
It was released April 26, 2019, by Universal Pictures.
The film explores themes of based on true story, impersonator, writer,
based on memoir or autobiography, male impersonator.
The tone is emotional.